gigpayrr.com 2015-12-05

# Privacy Policy - iPayrr

## User Protection Policy

At iPayrr, we value our users the most and therefore we walk an extra mile to ensure that their privacy is secured in the best way possible. We safeguard every bit of the user information and therefore we allow our users to remain anonymous, if they choose to be so, even while paying or being paid. 

With respect to cancellation of orders, buyers and sellers have the option of cancelling an order by mutual agreement. Late delivery or failure in delivering also leads to cancellation of an order but it results in a decrease in the seller’s rating. 

As a means of protection against any misconduct, iPayrr makes sure that no false feedback or ratings affect the reputation of a seller. It heavily guards any untrusted entity from using the website thus making it absolutely safe to use. We also safeguard our sellers from any kind of user misbehaviour. 

iPayrr boasts of 24x7 customer support services to attend to all your doubts and queries. Be it the account issues, orders or any kind of problem with our site, our customer support department is highly efficient in addressing all issues that concern your smooth operation of the site as well as deriving maximum benefit from it. 

We also have a highly competent team of moderators who maintain the superior quality of our site by eliminating any inappropriate content or spams. 

Even when we block the account of poor quality sellers, for an overall advantage of our site as well as our users, we ensure that they are able to withdraw their cleared earnings. In this way, our community remains clear of any poor quality sellers. 

## Privacy Policy

iPayrr respects the privacy of its users. Therefore, we ensure you, to the fullest extent, that your personal information is never divulged to any third party whatsoever. We assure that any information of personal identification you are asked to provide us with shall be in strict accordance with this privacy policy. 

This policy is subject to further modifications and alterations. Therefore, the users are advised to keep an eye on this page to remain updated on any changes, if and when made. 

While using our website, you may be asked to furnish certain information for personal identification reasons such as username, email, password, Paypal or Alertpay username and payout details etc by filling out online forms for specific services. However, you do have the option to choose whether or not these details can be used for direct marketing purposes. 

All information furnished by you will be used for providing you better services as they will help us in understanding your needs. Some of the records that we collect when you are transacting in our website include Log Files, Cookies and Web Beacons and DoubleClick Dart Cookie. Long File records that we collect include IP addresses type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), number of clicks, date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, track user’s movement and demographic information. 

DoubleClick Dart Cookie is used by Google for tracking your usage of our website, for interest based advertising. You also have the option of not using the DART cookie through visiting Google advertisement and privacy policy content network following the instructions laid down there. 

As for dealing with the third party vendors like ad servers and ad networks, it is advised that you go through their privacy policy separately for detailed information. However, with just few adjustments in your browser settings, you can easily disable third party cookies, if so required. You also need to remember that we do not have any control over the cookies those are in use by the external party advertisers. Also, we don’t have any access to them either. 

We use the information for record keeping, feedback requirements, improving the quality of the products and services offered, sending emails including product information, promotional offers and market research initiatives. We may also use the information provided by you to make moderations in our websites in accordance to your preferences, likes and dislikes. In all cases, our objective is to serve you better through continuous self evaluation and alterations. 

An important point to be remembered here is, when you navigate through the links of other websites provided in our URL, we cannot be held responsible for information protection and privacy. To avoid any unwanted situation, you may want to take a good look at the privacy statement of that website before furnishing any information to them. Usually, these links are of similar interest websites. 

As for accessing your information, it can be done anytime you wish to. Our privacy policy allows our users to access their personal data or make required moderations in user account settings. 

iPayrr guarantees absolute security of the personal information of its users by appropriate management and safeguarding processes. To avoid any case of unauthorized access, accidental loss of information or any other damage, we employ the best of our efforts through physical, electronic or managerial procedures.

Unless we have your permission or the law requires us to do so, you can be assured that any information furnished by you will not be sold, distributed or leased out to any third party. We also offer an option for restriction collection of personal information. For instance, if you are asked to fill in a form, you can select the box which says that you do not want to fill it. 

If you do not want us to use your personal information for direct marketing (which you had agreed to earlier) you can mail to us and inform us of the same at any point of time. The required alterations will be made from our end with immediate effect. You can also send us a mail if you wish to modify any information (which is incorrect or incomplete) provided earlier. 

## Disclaimer

Using information from this website is suggestive of your agreement to comply with the terms and conditions laid down by us. iPayrr reserves the authority to make any amendments or modifications without any prior notice, as such, and a continued use of our site even after any such changes implies that you are in perfect agreement with those changes.
